<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-05-26T13:49:17-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">the life of anj</title><subtitle>documenting my life :sunflower:</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Europe Trip Pt. 1 - Paris</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/22/europepart1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Europe Trip Pt. 1 - Paris" /><published>2023-05-22T08:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-05-22T08:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/22/europepart1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/22/europepart1.html">&lt;p&gt;Hellooooo my lovely friends. Welcome back to another post - this one is going to be long (as is the next one..lol) so feel free to skim, skip, and navigate this post in whatever way you’d like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s start off with some &lt;strong&gt;background&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just came back from Europe!!! Before this trip I had never been to Europe; I haven’t traveled internationally too much (only India and New Zealand and a Carnival Cruise to Mexico in 2nd grade which I don’t think counts) and I’ve been wanting to visit Europe for a long time now. But when I first thought about taking a trip, I didn’t even know how to begin planning it. I had no idea what areas to stay in, the kind of accommodations to book, train tickets, nothing; this was expected since I’d never been and my parents hadn’t either. I also didn’t have the energy or brain capacity to do all of the research, planning, and booking by myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was December 2022 and I wanted to book a trip before prices became too expensive. I was home for winter break and thinking of different ways I could travel to Europe. I thought of my dear friend Anuraag and the solo trip he took to Europe last year with gadventures, a travel company that did tours across the world (they even had tours specifically for 18-30somethings, which is what I was interested in). The idea of a tour group was appealing to me; I’d still get the “solo” element that I was looking for, because I wouldn’t know anyone in the group, but would also feel more safe and comfortable traveling with other people my age and being led by a tour guide. A strong pro for gadventures versus another kind of tour group (such as Contiki or Intrepid) was that I knew someone that had gone and enjoyed the trip. Once I made my decision, I booked the trip and kind of pushed it to the back of my mind for a couple of months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flash forward to May 2023. I hadn’t allowed myself to do much research about the places I’d be going on my trip. By that I mean I did no research at all. I kind of wanted to go on the trip with no expectations for the places I was traveling to. I didn’t want to have a checklist of things I had to do or things I had to see because I didn’t want to put pressure on myself during the actual trip. That turned out to be great for me and made the trip even more amazing than I had anticipated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s move on to the fun stuff. The trip had a very packed itinerary - we were on the move almost every 2 or 3 days, so things were moving very quickly. Here’s an outline of the trip:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;:round_pushpin: Day 1 - Land in Paris &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 2 - Paris &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 3 - Train to Interlaken, Switzerland &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 4 - Interlaken &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 5 - Interlaken &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 6 - Train to Rome, Italy &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 7 - Rome &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 8 - Train to Rapallo, Italy &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 9 - Rapallo &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 10 - Train to  Nice, France &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 11 - Nice, France &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 12 - Fly to Barcelona, Spain &lt;br /&gt;
:round_pushpin: Day 13 - Fly home &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah…pretty packed. This post is going to be kind of a day-by-day format, so feel free to skip around to the days that interest you :D. They were also written on the actual day the events took place, so just be aware that it is not in past tense, but in the present tense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before that, though let me introduce the CAST OF CHARACTERS. This might be kind of weird but I feel it’s necessary to put a face to the names of the people I will be talking about, just so you feel more involved in the storytelling lol. And yes, I had to make a table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The cast of characters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ladies: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Age&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Hometown&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Photo&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jordyn&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Canada&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;gym baddie + my trip bestie&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/jordyn.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rose&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;22&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Canada&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;French speaking girl from Quebec + also my trip bestie&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/rose.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Barbara (tour guide)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;28&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Italy&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;world traveler and coolest woman alive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/barbara.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Megan&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;27&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Australia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;motorbiking baddie&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/megan.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Casey&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;US&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;sweet but loved talking about herself&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/casey.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Georgia no. 1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;28&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;New Zealand&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;sweet adventurer&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/geo1.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Georgia no. 2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;28&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Australia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;divorced baddie with good sense of humor&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/geo2.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Melody&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;35&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Australia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;was 35 but seemed 25&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/melody.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Brianna&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;22&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;US&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mormon on her 3 year anniversary trip&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/brianna.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carlan&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;unknown&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Canada&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;high strung white girl who liked rosé&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/carlan.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Gents: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Age&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Hometown&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Photo&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ethan&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;22&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Canada&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;cutie with golden retriever energy who made a lot of dad jokes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/ethan.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Craig&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;23&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Canada&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ethan’s childhood bestie, also a gym baddie&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/craig.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Troy&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;29&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Canada&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;sweet guy, airline lost his luggage on the first day of his 26 day trip, musical theater kid energy&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/troy.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nick&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Australia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Indonesian who moved to Australia, very social, snored loudly&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/nick.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dino&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;26&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Australia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;My personal favorite man on this trip: the most wholesome energy, had an Australian accent straight out of H20 just add water&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/dino.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Spencer&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;24&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;US&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mormon married to Brianna&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/cast/spencer.png&quot; alt=&quot;jordyn&quot; width=&quot;50&quot; height=&quot;50&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;!-- The ladies: &lt;br&gt;
Jordyn - 20, F, Canada - gym baddie + my trip bestie &lt;br&gt;
Rose - 22, F, Canada - French speaking girl from Quebec + also my trip bestie &lt;br&gt;
Barbara (tour guide) - 28, F, Italy - world traveler and coolest woman alive &lt;br&gt;
Megan - 27, F, Australia - motorbiking baddie &lt;br&gt;
Casey - 21, F, US - sweet but loved talking about herself &lt;br&gt;
Georgia no. 1 - 28, F, Australia - divorced baddie with good sense of humor &lt;br&gt;
Georgia no. 2 - 28, F, New Zealand - sweet adventurer &lt;br&gt;
Melody - 35, F, Australia - was 35 but seemed 25 &lt;br&gt;
Carlan - unknown, F, Canada - high strung white girl who liked rosé &lt;br&gt;
Brianna - 22, F, US - Mormon on her 3 year anniversary trip &lt;br&gt;


The gents: &lt;br&gt;
Ethan - 22, M, Canada - cutie with golden retriever energy who made a lot of dad jokes &lt;br&gt;
Craig - 23, M, Canada - Ethan&apos;s childhood bestie, also a gym baddie &lt;br&gt;
Troy - 29, M, Canada - sweet guy, airline lost his luggage on ths first day of his 26 day trip &lt;br&gt;
Nick - 25, M, Australia - Indonesian who moved to Australia, very social &lt;br&gt;
Dino - 26, M, Australia - My personal favorite man on this trip: the most wholesome energy, had an Australian accent straight out of H20 just add water &lt;br&gt;
Spencer - 24, M, US - Mormon married to Brianna &lt;br&gt; --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 1 - 5/07 - arrival and first day in Paris&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Bonjour from Paris 🥖 🥐 🇫🇷  !! It feels surreal to actually be in Europe - I have been awaiting this day for many many months and it is BANANAS that it’s finally arrived. After two very manageable flights, I landed in Paris CDG airport at around 9:15am. When we landed, we got off the plane and straight into a bus that took us to border patrol, which took only about a half hour to go through. There was no customs, which was quite strange, and after I collected my luggage, I headed to the hostel address sent to us by the tour company. I wasn’t sure what to expect because we had not been given any contact information for our tour guide or other people in the tour group; I was basically going into it blind. There was the only the address we were supposed to meet at, so I hoped everything would work out and hopped in an uber to the hostel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I reached the hostel around 11 - it was a huge 9 story building filled with people and it had so much going on. There was a lovely common space, music, games, and people just talking and having a good time. I got the keys to my room and went upstairs - two girls had left their belongings in the room but no one else was actually there when I came in for the first time. I took a much needed shower and afterwards, felt ready to go on an adventure. My first mission was to get a croissant :croissant: . I mapped it to a bakery close by (there were so many so I just randomly picked one) and began my walk. As I was walking I took my time to just soak in the city; I would follow roads that looked appealing to me and walked inside shops that looked cute. My first impression was that Paris is adorable - everything was quaint and simple, and life seemed more enjoyable there. The buildings were so charming, and everyone was dining outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/firstday_streets.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;streets&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A funny thing about Paris is that they turn the chairs so that they all face the street; the people dining are basically enjoying a free show (watching the people on the street), and I could see them judging everyone that walked by. It was quite strange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I walked into a bakery called Liberte and got a chocolate croissant. One thing I didn’t expect was to be nervous walking into stores and ordering things; this is the first place I’ve ever been with a language barrier, and so I didn’t anticipate the nerves that came with that. But everyone speaks English so it ended up not being a problem.  I ate the croissant in under two minutes and went to explore more in search of a coffee. I walked by the canal and down lovely small streets lined with flowers and cute restaurants. I love the culture of eating outdoors despite the weather and how all the chairs face out towards the street. I got coffee at a cute place called La Fontaine, where the chef (and the place itself) looked straight out of Emily in Paris.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still hadn’t eaten lunch but had struggled to read menus and find veggie options in some places. I finally got a veg sandwich on a long thin baguette - it was delicious. But at this time, as I was strolling and eating the sandwich, it also started pouring. I made my way back to the hostel after my 2 hour adventure and changed out of my wet clothes. Soon after, I met my first roommate, Rose from Quebec! She spoke French but we managed to converse pretty well in English. I then took a 2 hour nap, before waking up again at 5:30. I met my second roommate, Jordyn, who is from Saskatchewan, Canada, and then we all headed down to the lobby to meet the rest of the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting everyone was SO NICE! There are 16 of us - a pretty big group. Our tour leader Barbara is this small Italian lady with a lot of energy and a sweet sweet personality. She brought her French boyfriend Pierre to meet us - he was also gorgeous. He looked like a French model and was the nicest person ever. We played two truths and a lie, and then headed out for a group dinner. It felt like Barbara and Pierre were our mom and dad, escorting us across the city.
Barbara made a reservation for us at this lovely place called Bouillon, which had a huge line of people waiting out the door. We got in immediately and were escorted upstairs to a huge room, filled with large parties. The restaurant was beautiful and filled with chatter and good vibes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/firstday_bouillon.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;bouillon&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dinner was so lovely and spent talking to new people. I sat with a couple of Australian girls and one Kiwi. Everyone is so sweet and chatty, which I loved. We drank and ate and had a lovely time together. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dinner everyone was exhausted so we headed back to the hostel to get ready for bed. My roomies - Jordyn, Casey, and Rose - and I stayed up chatting for a bit. I took a shower and then we all went to bed. It was such a good first day and I know it’s only going to get better from here! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 2 - 5/08 - Full day in Paris&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up early and started the day off with some hostel breakfast. It was kind of lame - just plain untoasted pieces of baguettes with jam and butter. I don’t think the French eat any real fruits or vegetables; honestly, I the meals I most frequently saw people eating were plain baguettes, baguettes with ham and cheese, or just cigarettes. lol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we had an orientation walk around Paris; basically that means that Barbara and Pierre took us on a tour around the city, showing us a lot of the highlights, taking us to some special viewpoints, and getting us some good food, like fresh croissants and sandwiches. We started off the walk by taking the Metro (not walking, ik)! It was so sleek and nice - I appreciated it because it was quite easy to navigate, even without google maps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first stop was Boulangerie 28, a delicious bakery where Barbara and Pierre got us fresh croissants and these heavenly chouquettes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/chouquette.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;sacrecoure&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We took our pastries to go and continued on our walk; we saw the grand City Hall, the Notre Dame, and spent time walking along the Seine. Babi and Pierre took us to this secret vewipoint where we could see the Louvre, boats on the river, and could people watch the Parisians - it was so lovely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/notredame.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;nd&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/seineviews.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;seine&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/secretspot.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;seine&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/seine_group.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;seine&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next stop was the Eiffel Tower. We took the metro to the Eiffel Tower stop and picked up food and groceries for a picnic. The whole group found a spot in the lawn by tower and had our picnic! It was definitely one of the highlights of the trip - very cute and wholesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/eiffeltower.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;et&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/picnic_group.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;picnic&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we took some more pics and the group split up (the mormons took a lot of couples pics lol). Some of the peeps and I headed over to the French pantheon and Latin quarter, and also spent some time walking around the Luxembourg gardens. We were all tired so then we went to the hostel to rest before the evening activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the evening, Pierre and Barbara took us on an adventure. We saw the Moulin Rouge building and the street lined with a bunch of sex shops (from Amelie!!). We got a dessert called a Marveilloux… it’s basically a super light Meringue filled with flavored cream. It was by far the most amazing dessert I’ve ever eaten. After that we walked through Montemart and to the Sacre Coure Basilica - one of my fav buildings to see in Paris! Montemart was so adorable and and had cute shops and restaurants lining the streets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/marveilloux.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;marveilloux&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/sacrecoure.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;sacrecoure&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dinner that night was at a tiny northern French specialty crepe place called Creperie Octopus. Barbara and Pierre took us here claiming that it was the most authentic French food we would get. And they were right… it was the best thing I ate in Paris (and looking back, one of the best things I ate the entire trip). The food was so authentic and good and fresh! We enjoyed our crepes with some specialty cider local to the north of France. I loved the whole evening and the weather, sunset, good company, and wonderful food made the energy perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/crepes.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;crepes&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dinner, we took the metro to the Eiffel Tower to see it sparkling at night! On the metro ride there, we witnessed a live pickpocketing!! But it was unsuccessful; the guy being pickpocketed caught the guy trying to steal from him…lol.
Seeing the glittering Eiffel tower truly was so beautiful. It seems very cheesy but seeing the dazzling tower made us all feel emotional and appreciative that we were on this trip together. There were couples dancing everywhere and someone playing some love songs and just the magic of the moment will stay with me for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We took the metro home and went to bed, exhausted froma long day of adventuring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/eiffelsparkling.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;eiffelsparkling&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 3 - 5/09 - Paris to Interlaken&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start the day off, Rose and I went to get breakfast - I got an INCREDIBLE pistachio cream filled croissant and a small latte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/pistacros.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;pistacros&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/paris/pistacro2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;pistacros&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two of us sat there and talked and ate for around 45 min before we headed out to shop. We took the metro to this area caled the Marais, where we walked along the main shopping street and stopped at cute French boutiques. Went to one called Nōs by Mirene, and Rose and I both fell in love with all of the stuff. I ended up getting a beautiful blue and green dress, and a lovely top. Then we window-shopped around some more before heading back to the hostel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was going to be a long transit day because we were traveling from Paris to Interlaken, Switzerland. From our hostel, we took the metro to the train station and spent some time at the boujee station. It was so fancy - like a mini airport! It had amazing patisseries and shops inside. I got a macaron and a marveilloux while waiting for our train. Finally, we got aboard the train to Basel. The train ride was so nice and just a chance to chat with and get to know our group mates a little better. Afterwards, we got off at Basel train station and took the train to our step, Interlaken Ost. When we got there it was pouring and we had to walk in the rain to our hostel with all our luggage, which was quite unpleasant. Finally, we got there and settled in - our group went out for a chill dinner and afterwards, were all very tired so we passed out asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to make shorter posts so that they are easier to take in and because there are just a ton of details about this trip that I want to share. Stay tuned for the next couple of posts! Side note:  I put a decent amount of effort into making that table up there and I’m quite proud of it…hehe. Hopefully you can use it as a reference in my future posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xoxo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">Hellooooo my lovely friends. Welcome back to another post - this one is going to be long (as is the next one..lol) so feel free to skim, skip, and navigate this post in whatever way you’d like.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Europe Trip Pt. 2 - Interlaken and Rome</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/22/europepart2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Europe Trip Pt. 2 - Interlaken and Rome" /><published>2023-05-22T08:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-05-22T08:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/22/europepart2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/05/22/europepart2.html">&lt;p&gt;Another day, another post…welcome back to the blog, my friends. Yes, this is coming out very soon after the previous post, but that’s just because all of these posts are about the same trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the previous post, we had just arrived in Interlaken, Switzerland (Day 3). Before we get into the details, I wanted to talk a little bit about Interlaken. Basically, it became popular because of Yash Chopra, the Bollywood director :clapper:. When we first reached the city, I saw a ton of Indian people but didn’t think twice about it - Indian tourists are everywhere (I know that because I am one…lmao). So naturally, I just assumed they loved Switzerland and mountains. But on the first day of the tour, Barbara took us to a statue - yes, a full on shiny bronze statue - of Yash Chopra and explained his significance in the city. He became an ambassador of Interlaken because he brought the Bollywood industry to Switzerland, most significantly with DDLJ. That brought a whole new market of tourism to the country, which is pretty awesome :sparkles:.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, Interlaken was a beautiful place. A quaint city nestled amongst a staggering mountainscape and surrounded by clear turquoise lakes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/interlaklake.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/interlakquaint.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was way more commercial than I expected - despite how small it was, it was packed with luxury goods stores, chocolatiers, restaurants, and people. The four days we spent in Interlaken and Rome were my favorite part of the entire Europe trip, and for good reason. The whole tour group became close, and this was when we started to make more meaningful connections with one another. Now, on to the day by day deets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 4 - 5/10 - First full day in Interlaken&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
We all woke up pretty early and had breakfast in the hostel (which was actually a huge upgrade from the Paris hostel breakfast…lol). The hostel itself was also very boujee; we had a balcony that looked out onto the mountains and because of the rain and mist there was this mystical vibe all around :mountain_snow:. We were supposed to start the day off with an orientation walk around the city followed by a hike but Barbara ended up canceling the hike because of the rain (which ended up subsiding anyway). So everyone kind of split up to do whatever they wanted to. The Mormons were going up to Lauterbrunnen, so a few of the other girls and I decided to go up there as well. Lauterbrunnen was a small little mountain town that was a short train ride away from Interlaken. It was supposed to be very quaint and filled with waterfalls (and it had cows!!), so I was excited to get up there. The five of us - Casey, Brianna, Spencer, Rose, and I - were waiting to catch the train in Interlaken when a girl came up to us at the station and started making conversation. Turns out she was making her way up to Lauterbrunnen too, but didn’t have anyone to go with. Naturally, we invited her to join us on her adventure; we found out her name was Britt and she was a 19 year old from Amsterdam just finished up her 7 week solo trip across Europe! We got on the train and had some pleasant conversations as we made our way up the mountain :mountain_railway:. Once we reached, we embarked on a hike through the Valley of 72 Waterfalls. I don’t know what I was expecting, but whatever expectations I had were far exceeded by the beauty of the scenery. It was absolutely stunning, just like the Switzerland you see in photos. The whole landscape was lush and green, filled with cows and waterfalls and dotted with old wooden houses. It was the scene out of a movie, and the scale of the landscape combined with the quaintness of the buildings created such an incredible setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/lauthouses.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/selfiewaterfalls.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/sugardonutslaut.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/aestheticswitz.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We walked there for two hours and then got some mini donuts, followed by lunch - I had a raclette, which is just veggies covered in cheese with spices. After lunch, the 6 of us came back down to Interlaken and split up. Rose and I shopped a little bit - we got some hot chocolate made from fresh 65% cocoa bits and it’s the best hot cocoa I’ve had in my whole life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/food/europe/raclette.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/freshhotchoc.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/prettymountainsfromtown.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, we spent some time getting ready for dinner - we were taking the tram :tram: up to the highest peak in Interlaken, called Harder Kulm. There was a restaurant up there with the best views of the city. We enjoyed the lovely vistas and ate fondue, which tasted too much like wine though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/harderkulm.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/harderkulmview.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/fondue.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The restaurant had a house dog (cutest concept ever) and he was a BIG BOY Bernese mountain dog named Hardy - I loved him so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/hardy1.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/hardy2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dinner, we all came down and still wanted to hang out before going to bed. We played table tennis, card games, and talked in the game room for a few hours before sleeping. It was the first time we all really gathered to spend quality time doing nothing but having some good old-fashioned fun while getting to know each other. A very wholesome night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 5 - 5/11 - Second full day in Interlaken&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
I Woke up pretty early and had breakfast with the rest of the crew downstairs. Today I was going on a solo adventure to Jungfrau, which is the highest accessible peak in Europe! The highlight up there was the stunning views of the surrounding mountainscape. But since it was really rainy and misty, I knew that the views were not going to be the best. After eating, I made my way to the train station and asked the people at the station to help map out the path for me. First, I took the train to the Grindelwald terminal, followed by a cable car up to Eigerletscher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/eiger.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I got off the cable car :mountain_cableway: and stepped into the station, I could see through the windows that the station was surrounded by white, snow covered mountains. I went outside to see what the air was like and stepped into the most beautiful powdery snow. It was actively snowing and walking in the soft snow was surreal (Californians really don’t know how to react to snow lol). It was quiet all around me and all I could hear was the wintery sounds of the mountains. I got emotional just being there and thinking about how lucky I was to be having these experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/meinsnow.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next I took the train up to Jungfrau, which was awesome. Once I reached Jungfrau, I took my time waking through all of the things up there. The view was completely clouded out (sadness) from the observatory; literally, all I could see was white all around me. But, I went out to the glacier viewpoint and saw some lovely mountains and more snow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/jungfrau.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/jungflag.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also went to the Lindt chocolate shop and got myself a few truffles because why shouldn’t I. I was having the time of my life! But then I decided to leave and go back down to Interlaken. Surprisingly, that ended up being the most awesome part of the whole experience (not the leaving part, but the cable car ride down)!! I took the Eiger Express cable car down and the view when we departed was STUNNINGGGG!! :mountain_snow:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/waydowneiger.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/switz/eigerview.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;switzy&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The clouds had cleared up and the mountainscape was in full display - it looked like a National Geographic magazine cover. Everyone on the tram oohed and aahed as we left the terminal and it was the most gorgeous. Once I came down, I went to the grocery store to pick up some salad and then hung out with Rose. We got some chocolate from the Swiss chocolate chalet, and then some hot choc from another store (it was literally just melted chocolate and not that good). That evening we were pooped - we all went to a nice dinner at this cute German brasserie and then came back and crashed because we had to be up at 6am the next day for our private bus to Milan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 6 - 5/12 - Travel from Interlaken to Rome&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
An early morning - we woke up at 5:15 because we had to be in the lobby of the hostel by 5:55. I got ready and we boarded the private bus that was taking us to Milan. We got on and I fell asleep almost instantly; two hours later we reached our first stop, a little cafe / shop in the Italian part of Switzerland, and I had a Nutella filled croissant before we continued the journey to Milan. We reached the Milan train station and had around an hour to eat - our first taste of real Italian food! I got an arancini and a Maritozzo - both of which were delish (Maritozzo pictured below) - but I wanted to save the pizza pasta experience for the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/maricase.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/maritozzo.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon after, we boarded the train from Milan to Rome! It was not too long a ride, but we then had to sprint across the train station in Rome to catch the final train to our hostel station - it was a sweaty time LOL. Finally we reached the Roma Trastevere station and got off. We walked around ten minutes to our hostel, and had 40 min before we had to leave again to go out. The bathroom sitch was weird because six of us girls had to share a huge bathroom with the 6 guys? But it worked out fine lol. I quickly showered and changed into a cute summer outfit because it was FINALLY the first warm day of the trip :sunny:!! Then around 5:30, we left on our evening adventure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/meandcarlanrome.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to preface the next part of my day by saying this was the best part of the trip. I don’t think I can ever capture how special or wonderful the whole evening was, but it was magic and the feeling will stay with me forever. We left the hostel at 5:30 and took the bus to a special viewpoint of the Colosseum that Barbara wanted to take us to. We spent a little time taking pictures at the spot and took some group pics too! Then we embarked on our walk through the city. We went through the whole Colosseum and Roman Forum area, and saw a bunch of the historical, grand buildings - the architecture everywhere was truly grand. It was even more incredible because we were out at golden hour, it was warm outside, and the evening sunlight was glowing and reflecting on all of these massive buildings - it was so spectacular. :city_sunset:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/meandroserome.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/goldenhourrome.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We walked through the town and got to a cute little bar, where we finally got our first aperol spritzes :tropical_drink:! To go, actually, which was cool. Europe is crazy because you can drink on the streets, which is very illegal literally everywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/cutebar.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/apspritzbar.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We took our spritzes to go on our walk to the restaurant, which was in Trastevere, the most lively part of the city. The whole walk there was so charming and it felt like I was in a movie (ik I’ve said that about all of the places so far, but this was the epitome of that feeling). The streets were picturesque and the lights were turning on and the whole city came alive on the warm, glowy Friday evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/trastaverebridge.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/romebridge.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went to an amazing restaurant selected by Barbara and feasted on the best Italian food I’ve ever had. We got AMAZINGGGG Napoli style pizza and fresh Cacio e Pepe pasta. Ended with some Tiramisu. It was the perfect meal and everything tasted heavenly (we were also all starving, which helped).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/food/europe/napolipizza.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/food/europe/cacioepepe.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/food/europe/tiramisu.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dinner we went next door to a gelato place where I got stracciatella gelato (it was amazing) :ice_cream:. Then to a bar called Delirium - we got some drinks and then went out into the streets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/food/europe/gelato2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/deliriumbar.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/teqshots.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The streets were loud and filled with young people and the smell of food and cigarettes. The lights were on and people were happy to be out on such a perfect night where the weather was very conducive to shenanigans. We went to this tiny shop called Bum Bum Bar to get cheap drinks that were served over fresh fruit - and then we drank in the streets!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/bumbumbar.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/memegan.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/romestreets.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone was a little tipsy and having the best time being with one another on our last night together in Rome. We stayed in the streets for a while just enjoying life to the fullest. After that, we were about to go into a club but the men were denied because they were wearing sandals…so we left. I ended up going home but some people stayed out. I came home, showered and went to bed at 1:30 after having the perfect evening and night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 6 - 5/13 - Full day in Rome&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
The day was a little strange because 1) we knew it could never be as good as the previous day and 2) the rain threw everything off. Jordyn and I got up, ate breakfast and then headed to the Colosseum for our tour, which ended up being a waste of time and money. It was cool for a few minutes, but that’s all I really needed in the Colosseum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/mejordancol.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We then got a cappuccino from some cafe (so good btw). Coffee culture in Italy is very interesting - people usually order and drink their coffees at the bar, and they usually get something small like a cappuccino or, more commonly, just an espresso shot (quite nasty, actually). It’s meant to be more of a quick refuel rather than something to sit and enjoy. :coffee:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, Jordyn and I walked towards the Roman Forum, but the line to get in was so long and the rain so hard that we decided to abandon it and walk to Trastevere for lunch (food &amp;gt; historical sights am I right). We got there and went to a restaurant called Nonarella, where I had a bufalina pizza (it was avg! way too much cheese).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/food/europe/pizza.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After lunch Jordyn and  we went shopping for a bit. I got an authentic Italian leather jacket - my dream jacket - from this Italian leather store and then we walked back to the hostel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/romerain.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/travel/italy/romerain2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We met up with Dino, and then Dino and I took a little walk up to a gelato shop. Dino is such good company and we had a good conversation walking to the gelato place. I got a PHENOMENAL strawberry mint lime gelato - just wow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/food/europe/strawmintgelato.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;italia&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dino and I came back to the hostel, and then we had some downtime before meeting up with our new group members! And a new tour leader. Basically, our original group would be splitting up because some people were going to continue up North towards Eastern Europe and some of us were going South towards Spain. That meant leaving behind some friends and Barbara :( Our new tour guide was a Spaniard named Carlos, who was very sweet. We met with Carlos and the five new girls, who were all nice. But the vibes were not the same and I don’t think they will be for the rest of the trip. The first half was so good that it set such a high standard for the rest of it :( which is good but also I’m not sure how closely the new group will connect for the rest of it. We met Barbara’s group for a final round of drinks and goodbyes and then called it a night by 11:30.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GUYS it only gets better from here. Stay tuned for the next post (or two) about the second half of the trip. As always, thank you for reading and tuning in. Check out my new &lt;a href=&quot;/pages/europetripfood&quot;&gt;Europe Foods&lt;/a&gt; page for some more pics hehe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xoxo&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">Another day, another post…welcome back to the blog, my friends. Yes, this is coming out very soon after the previous post, but that’s just because all of these posts are about the same trip.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Moving out of San Diego</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/04/26/movingoutofsd.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moving out of San Diego" /><published>2023-04-26T07:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-04-26T07:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/04/26/movingoutofsd</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/04/26/movingoutofsd.html">&lt;p&gt;(Hi guys sorry I fixed the link)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Helloooo everyone - I left San Diego!! Which seems bizarre to think about, but it’s happened. I think packing up my boxes into the car and finally emptying out my room made it feel like I was finally done with college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After coming back from New York, I was actually pretty sick but tried to ignore the fact that I was sick so it was just me not taking care of myself and then getting sicker. It was not great lol. But I spent the first week back going kickboxing, hitting my favorite coffee shops (also peep my new &lt;a href=&quot;/pages/coffeeshops&quot;&gt;coffee shops&lt;/a&gt; page on the blog hehe) and packing up my room. There was more to pack then I anticipated but I would just put on some music or YouTube videos and grind for a couple hours to get things packed. Going through all of the stuff in my room was strange because 1) I realized I have way too many clothes and have a serious shopping issue but also 2) that college went by insanely fast. I found brochures for school events, notebooks from my freshman year classes, and birthday cards from friends; it was crazy to think that this phase of my life is coming to an end and I’ll have to leave behind a lot of the people and memories that made college wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sunday the 16th I made a day trip to USC to take grad pics for Aditi and her friends. I always love being on the USC campus because it’s everything that UCSD is not lol; it’s a small, lovely campus with the typical brick-building feel that I always associate with colleges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/16_04_aditi.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;me aditi lulu&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/16_04_aditi2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;me aditi&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent the day there taking pictures for her and her friends - I always love seeing Aditi because whenever we spend time together it’s like no time has passed in between. But I think being out all day made my ongoing sickness even worse and the next morning I woke up with no voice and a painfully raw sore throat lol. :face_with_thermometer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent Monday resting at home in bed, but then felt better enough to go out again on Tuesday. I kept up with kickboxing, coffee drinking, and seeing people. It was actually so great and much needed quality time with my friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/19_04_manav.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;manavs house&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/14_04_brunch.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;ritika brunch&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also spent a lot of quality time with Anya and Siyona, which is always really nice. The weather starting getting really nice towards the end of the week, and the three of us went out on a cute coffee date to MRKT space on Thursday, and just talked for a long time. I saw Varun that evening and we watched the sunset at Gliderport, which was gorgeous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/20_04_gliderport.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;gp1&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/20_04_gp2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;gp2&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was such a perfect day. I started off the day with kickboxing - my last class :sadface: Anya, Siyona, and I had a beach day on Friday because the weather was in the 70s - we packed a picnic and hung out at Del Mar beach for a couple of hours :ocean:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/21_04_beach.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;girls at the beach&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/21_04_beach2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;beach view&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/21_04_picnic.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;picnic&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was actually warm enough to swim in the ocean, which was so lovely. I lost my sunglasses to the ocean - a sacrifice that I was not ready to make. After the beach we went to some rooftop complex close by and just sat there for a while chatting, drinking coffee, and decompressing. It’s so nice to have no responsibilities right now because I can fully enjoy days like that, spent relaxing and just living life without any hassle. We watched the sunset that evening and then Anya, Saket, and I got dinner together at Buona Forchetta South Park, which is one of my favorite Italian places in SD. We finished the night up with the new season of Indian Matchmaking and then went to bed. It was such a good day!! :sunny:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/21_04_sunset.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;gp day 2&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday was the day my parents were coming down from the Bay Area. They were coming down on Saturday to SD and we were going to drive back home on Sunday. I started off the morning by going to Holsem Coffee in North Park (one of my favorite shops) and got a bagel and coffee for myself to start the day :coffee: I also went to Pigment and got myself some new sunglasses :sunglasses:. My parents were arriving later that day so I did some cleaning and last minute packing before they came. They finally arrived at around 3:30pm, and we went to La Jolla Shores for some food and beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/22_04_beach.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;lj shores&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I took them to Liberty Station - we hung out at Moniker and drank some good coffee before going to the Public Market and getting some food. Then we headed home to pack up the car with all of my stuff (mostly clothes…lol). My parents, my roommates and I chatted for some time which was cute. The roomies and I watched some more Indian Matchmaking and then went to bed. :zzz:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My parents and I left San Diego and started our drive home at around 9:30 the next morning, with a long car ride ahead of us. We love to make a lot of stops lol so I knew we’d be on the road for at least 10 hours. On the way home we stopped in Santa Barbara :palm_tree: it was my first time there and I reallyyyyy loved it. After a couple of stops and a lot of driving (none of it done by me because my dad wouldn’t let me drive) we made it home at 10pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/23_04_sb.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;santa barbara&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been 3 days since coming home and I’ve been just enjoying relaxing and being pampered. The weather has been in the 70s and 80s and I sit in the backyard everyday soaking in the sun and working on this blog. My neighbors dog barks at me frequently from his backyard - he’s kind of a brat to me but he loves my parents. His name is Buddy and he hangs out at my house sometimes - my parents take care of him when they miss the feeling of having a child in the house. But when I’m back home, he doesn’t come over too much because he knows I’m the princess of the household and he can’t compete with that. There are a lot of birds in the backyard - hummingbirds, robins, huge crows (which scare me) and a ton more. As I’m writing this, the crow and I are having a stare-down. All of the birds come and bathe in the many fountains and birdbaths my parents have in the yard. Our orange tree has a lot of blossoms right now and smells so good, and our pear tree is finally blossoming!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blog has been keeping me very occupied. I spent the whole day yesterday trying to figure out how to make an image carousel (again, check out the new &lt;a href=&quot;/pages/coffeeshops&quot;&gt;coffee shops&lt;/a&gt; page for an example) and just refining some of the features. With jekyll these features have to all be manually created and added so it’s a little time consuming. The blog will be changing frequently so don’t be surprised if it looks different every time you open it lol. It’s nice being home but I don’t really leave the house at all. I feel like I’m in this weird limbo space because I’m in between different phases of my life right now. It’s nice but also I’ve never been one to enjoy having nothing to do - I miss my routine and work too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ANYWAYS, thank you for reading and being a subscriber to this blog. Even if you’re an involuntary subscriber and I just added you to the email list lol. This is my first time using the email list btw!! So let me know if there’s anything I should add / change / any suggestions you have for the blog in general. Stay tuned for more updates :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/25_04_home.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;coffee backyard&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">(Hi guys sorry I fixed the link)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">First Day of the Blog!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/04/03/first-day.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Day of the Blog!" /><published>2023-04-03T17:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-04-03T17:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/04/03/first-day</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/04/03/first-day.html">&lt;!-- &lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/03_04_gotan1.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;gotan1&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height= &quot;400&quot;/&gt; --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!!!! First day of the blog AHHHHHH!!
This is a lie because I am actually writing this three days after I made the blog…lol.
But yeah I was feeling really bored with my time off and decided to make a website because it’s something that I’ve been wanting to do for a long time and now I finally have free time to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The creation of the blog was a slightly lengthy process because I really wanted to use Jekyll - it’s been recommended so many times to me as an efficient way to make a website and I mostly liked that it gave a really clean output. So, I sat at this cute cafe in nyc called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gotancafe.com/&quot;&gt;Gotan&lt;/a&gt; in Tribeca and learned how to use Jekyll. The cafe was really cute and I loved the aesthetic but it was lowkey wack because there was no wifi…but there were outlets??? So they didn’t want people working but still gave outlets??? idk it was a very confusing situation. But I ended up staying there for around three-four hours. I was actually there to meet Heramb, one of my brother’s close friends and also now one of my friends, but he came two hours late so I was just watching Jekyll tutorials for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some cute pics of the cafe!
&lt;!-- ![gotan1](anjsri878.github.io/loats/assets/img/03_04_gotan1.JPG) --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/03_04_gotan1.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;gotan1&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/03_04_gotan2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;gotan2&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The coffee was alright and so was the oatmeal…but also I don’t think I was in the position to be judging their food because I could not really eat properly. BASICALLY I’ve been having trouble because my wisdom teeth are growing in and for the past week I could not open my mouth more than half and inch because my left jaw is inflamed. So yeah eating food has been really not fun and actually quite painful. I have been sticking to coffee, smoothies, soups, and it kinda sucks :sweat:. I definitely need to come back to this place to try their sandos though because they looked really yum. Heramb got this herb omelette sandwich and it looked :fire:.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a couple of hours of working though, I got quite hungry. The coffee and oatmeal were definitely not enough to sustain me until dinner, so I went to find some ramen. Heramb suggested Danbo Ramen, which was in the West Village, around a 20 minute walk up from the cafe. I got there and sat by myself at the counter, and ordered their classic vegan ramen, which came with a vegan broth, thin noodles, scallions, sliced tofu and kikurage (wood ear mushrooms). Oh man that ramen was SO GOOD and hit the spot. It was still kind of hard to eat because of my jaw but I took my time and finished as much of it as I could. Definitely a 10/10 and one of the best ramens I’ve had. And it was only around $15 total!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/03_04_danbo.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;danbo&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After ramen it was almost time for me to go back home so I just stalled time for a little bit and decided to get tea (remember the only reason I was drinking so many liquids it because solid food was nearly impossible for me to fit in my mouth lmao). I just kinda walked around until I found a cute one called Amano Cafe - I just got a mint tea :tea: and then caught the F train back to Brooklyn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gallery/03_04_tea.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;amano&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent the evening watching Atlanta and drinking a smoothie before going to bed. :zzz:&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>